<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>My Family Aid</title>
	<atom:link href="/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2023 21:02:38 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.4.3</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/sites/98/2023/10/cropped-myfamilyaid-favicon-32x32.jpeg</url>
	<title>My Family Aid</title>
	<link>/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Mom’s Mouth-watering Pumpkin Pie Recipe With a Secret Bomb Crust</title>
		<link>/2023/10/05/moms-mouth-watering-pumpkin-pie-recipe-with-a-secret-bomb-crust/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[eisel]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2023 21:00:46 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Family Kitchen]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://myfamilyaid.globalwebsitesadmin.com/?p=483</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<div class="et_pb_section et_pb_section_0 et_section_regular" >
				
				
				
				
				
				
				<div class="et_pb_row et_pb_row_0">
				<div class="et_pb_column et_pb_column_4_4 et_pb_column_0  et_pb_css_mix_blend_mode_passthrough et-last-child">
				
				
				
				
				<div class="et_pb_module et_pb_text et_pb_text_0  et_pb_text_align_left et_pb_bg_layout_light">
				
				
				
				
				<div class="et_pb_text_inner"><p><strong>Recipe</strong><span></span><br /><span>2 whole pre-made Trader Joe’s gingerbread Molasses cookie dough as Pie Crust</span><br /><span>1 can of Organic Pumpkin (usually from Trader Joe’s or Wholefoods)</span><br /><span>½ Cup of Brown Sugar</span><br /><span>½  Cup of butter</span><br /><span>½ Cup white Sugar</span><br /><span>3 Large eggs</span><br /><span>1 Can of sweetened condensed milk</span><br /><span>1 Stick of melted butter</span><br /><span>1 Teaspoon of Vanilla Extract</span><br /><span>1 Teaspoon of cinnamon</span></p>
<p><span></span></p>
<p><strong>Directions</strong><span></span><br /><span>1. Pre-heat oven to 350F getting ready for the Trader Joe’s Gingerbread Molasses Cookie Dough</span></p>
<p><span>2. Then let bake for 15-20 minutes and let cool for 2 minutes after your dough is cooled and putting some baking powder on the counter.</span></p>
<p><span>3. Combine the cookie dough into a ball then use a dough roller to flatten out the dough at a slime thick consistency.</span></p>
<p><span>4. Use the inside of your backing pan also use the side to build up the dough crust with four extra stored Ginger Cookie Dough. To then refrigerate and cool.</span></p>
<p><span>5. For the Pumpkin Pie Crack two eggs whisk thoroughly.</span></p>
<p><span>6. Melt the butter in the microwave to a melt.</span></p>
<p><span>7. Place the Flour, Vanilla Extract, Sugar, Cinnamon, Salt inside after the butter has cooled a little. Mix With a whisk.</span></p>
<p><span>8. To Then put the canned Pumpkins in after mix with a mixer machine and place the sweetened condensed milk in and mix again with the mixer.</span></p>
<p><span>9. Take out the cooled dough and then place the batter to be baked at 350F for 1 1/2 hours. </span></p></div>
			</div>
			</div>
				
				
				
				
			</div>
				
				
			</div>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Best Family Cars for 2021</title>
		<link>/2023/10/05/best-family-cars-for-2021/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[eisel]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2023 20:57:05 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News & Insight]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://myfamilyaid.globalwebsitesadmin.com/?p=477</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<div class="et_pb_section et_pb_section_1 et_section_regular" >
				
				
				
				
				
				
				<div class="et_pb_row et_pb_row_1">
				<div class="et_pb_column et_pb_column_4_4 et_pb_column_1  et_pb_css_mix_blend_mode_passthrough et-last-child">
				
				
				
				
				<div class="et_pb_module et_pb_text et_pb_text_1  et_pb_text_align_left et_pb_bg_layout_light">
				
				
				
				
				<div class="et_pb_text_inner"><p>You&#8217;re a family of four, and you need to find the best car that will work for all of your needs. You want something fun but also practical! Luckily, we&#8217;ve compiled a list of the best family cars in 2021 so this decision won&#8217;t be quite as hard. Read on for our top picks!</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<h3>3 Best Family Cars of 2021</h3>
<p>The best family cars of 2021 are not just transportation &#8211; they are a connection to society for all those who take it for granted. They offer us more than what is expected with roominess and convenience, so if you&#8217;re looking for one as your next vehicle, these best family cars will be sure to please everyone in the backseat.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<h3>1. Honda Odyssey</h3>
<p>Families are best with the best of both worlds &#8211; space and convenience. The Honda Odyssey has been a longstanding favorite among families for years. So, if you&#8217;re looking for something reliable that won&#8217;t let you down when it comes to family trips and daily errands around town, this car is your best bet.</p>
<p>The Honda Odyssey is a great choice because it is spacious and convenient. The Honda Odyssey is often considered the best long-term investment among families since it’s reliable, spacious, and affordable! How does it drive? Its V-turbo engine gives you ample power in places like mountains or rocky areas. It also fits easily into small parking spaces without sacrificing comfort with its compact dimensions. Plus, safety features are standard so everyone inside the vehicle feels secure on both sides of the windshield. This car should be your pick if you want something that will last.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<h3>2. Chrysler Pacifica</h3>
<p>Chrysler Pacifica is the best family car of 2021 because it offers the best of both worlds. It&#8217;s a crossover that can be used as an SUV or for business purposes. Chrysler Pacifica also has an attractive exterior design and comfortable seating arrangement with well-equipped interior space to keep everyone happy on long trips. The Chrysler Pacifica comes in three trim levels: L, LX, and Touring Plus. All trims are equipped with premium safety features, such as adaptive cruise control, which means you will never have to worry about hitting anything from behind when driving at high speeds. ​</p>
<p>Refreshes insides out for 2021, the Pacifica feels like you are driving on a cloud. It&#8217;s known for its exceptional handling and great control. Plus, when you have kids sitting in the back, you want a car that handles well on the road.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<h3>3. Kia Sedona</h3>
<p>Another entry on our list of the best family car for 2021 is the Kia Sedona. It has a large cabin that can fit four adults and three kids comfortably, making road trips easier without any worries of cramped cabins or uncomfortable seats. The Kia Sedona also comes in three trim levels: LX, EX, and SX Luxury, which means you will be able to find one with your specific needs no matter how big or small they may be! Plus, this vehicle was designed with safety as its number one priority so it&#8217;s never been safer than before to have your loved ones travel inside while out on the open road.</p></div>
			</div>
			</div>
				
				
				
				
			</div>
				
				
			</div>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Questions to Ask Yourself Before Having Your First Child</title>
		<link>/2023/10/05/questions-to-ask-yourself-before-having-your-first-child/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[eisel]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2023 20:54:17 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News & Insight]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://myfamilyaid.globalwebsitesadmin.com/?p=472</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<div class="et_pb_section et_pb_section_2 et_section_regular" >
				
				
				
				
				
				
				<div class="et_pb_row et_pb_row_2">
				<div class="et_pb_column et_pb_column_4_4 et_pb_column_2  et_pb_css_mix_blend_mode_passthrough et-last-child">
				
				
				
				
				<div class="et_pb_module et_pb_text et_pb_text_2  et_pb_text_align_left et_pb_bg_layout_light">
				
				
				
				
				<div class="et_pb_text_inner"><p>When you and your partner are ready to have a baby, your mind is often consumed with the thoughts of creating a new family and the fun you’ll have to do it. As important as it is to enjoy having a baby, you need to start family planning. Raising a child in the current economic conditions is not easy. Your finances will be hurt, and you might drown in bills every month. In this blog post, we will help you with family planning and share a list of questions you should ask yourself before having your first child. So, let’s get started! </p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<h3>Questions to Ask Yourself Before Having Your First Child</h3>
<p>There might be many things on your mind when you are ready to have your first baby. However, you should streamline your worries and ask yourself relevant questions before trying. Here is a list of things you should sort out before planning your first child. </p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<h3>Are Your Finances in Good Shape?</h3>
<p>One of the most important questions when having your first child is to check if your finances are in good shape. You can do this by calculating your net worth. Divide your assets with liabilities (loan or due payments); this will help you identify your worth. Plus, check your potential salary growth in your field of work. If your company has room for higher positions, having a baby is the best decision. Otherwise, you would need to switch your job to a better company. </p>
<h3></h3>
<h3>What&#8217;s Your Job&#8217;s Paternity/Maternity Policy?</h3>
<p>Having a baby is fun until you realize that you are not financially strong enough so both parents have to work. In this case, you need to ask your employer about your workplace’s maternity/paternity leave policy. These leaves are also important for the father because you will be spending half of your day catering to your wife’s needs after your child’s birth. </p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<h3>Are You Ready for More Chores?</h3>
<p>Having a baby means more work. If your career has just started, planning a baby might not be in your best interest. However, if you think you are at the peak of your career and can handle additional responsibilities, go for it. Otherwise, you might have to give up on your career, and this goes for both parents. </p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<h3>What Religion Will Your Baby Follow?</h3>
<p>Interreligious marriages are common in the USA, and everything seems fine until you plan to have your first baby. During this period, you should discuss which religion your child will follow. However, inmost cases, parents leave this decision on their children to choose whatever religion they would be interested in. </p>
<h3></h3>
<h3>Ending Note</h3>
<p>Having your first child is not easy. You’ll have more responsibilities, and your finances will be hurt in the first few months after the baby arrives. In this situation, it’s best to talk out things and also discuss how you will raise the child. The questions mentioned above are a good start to a meaningful conversation between soon-to-be parents. </p></div>
			</div>
			</div>
				
				
				
				
			</div>
				
				
			</div>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Top 10 Places to Travel for Families</title>
		<link>/2023/10/05/top-10-places-to-travel-for-families/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[eisel]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2023 20:41:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News & Insight]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://myfamilyaid.globalwebsitesadmin.com/?p=467</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<div class="et_pb_section et_pb_section_3 et_section_regular" >
				
				
				
				
				
				
				<div class="et_pb_row et_pb_row_3">
				<div class="et_pb_column et_pb_column_4_4 et_pb_column_3  et_pb_css_mix_blend_mode_passthrough et-last-child">
				
				
				
				
				<div class="et_pb_module et_pb_text et_pb_text_3  et_pb_text_align_left et_pb_bg_layout_light">
				
				
				
				
				<div class="et_pb_text_inner"><p>As the world reopens after the COVID-19lockdown, it is only fair that you’d want to take your family on vacation someplace far away. However, traveling to certain countries with children can be difficult even when we’re not in the middle of a pandemic. Don’t worry! We’ve compiled a list of the top 10 places to travel to for families so that you don’t have to spend hours researching the destination you wish to visit. You will still have to check in to know if all of these companies are open for tourism, but here are some of our picks! </p>
<h3></h3>
<h3>Singapore</h3>
<p>It’s a small country, but it’s filled with activities for you and your kids to enjoy. You can visit Universal Studios or even enjoy some of the futuristic gardens. Singapore’s national language is English. So, you shouldn’t find traveling from one place to another difficult. </p>
<h3></h3>
<h3>Vietnam</h3>
<p>Vietnam is a great country to visit with children. It has beaches and many historical sites. You can walk around towns and learn about the Vietnam War or enjoy nature at the Mekong Delta. </p>
<h3></h3>
<h3>Japan</h3>
<p>It is one of the best countries to visit regardless of the size and age of your family. It is a clean and safe country with many exciting activities for you to take on with your family. You can go hiking or rafting and visit some of the most architecturally beautiful places in Asia. </p>
<h3></h3>
<h3>France</h3>
<p>France is home to several museums and galleries that make it an excellent great historical site to visit as a child. Even if your child is not a big history buff, the Eiffel Tower at night is enough to hold anyone’s gaze. Additionally, French food is to die for. </p>
<h3></h3>
<h3>Malaysia</h3>
<p>It is a great gateway country to Southeast Asia if you’ve never traveled here. It has beautiful clean beaches and tropical resorts where you and your family can witness nature at its finest. Malaysia is also home to many cultures. So, it’s a great way to introduce your children to different cultures. </p>
<h3></h3>
<h3>Coast Rica</h3>
<p>With its natural parks and beaches, Costa Rica is one of the most visited sites in Central America. You can take your kids ziplining or horseback riding even if they’re young, so they can thoroughly enjoy themselves. </p>
<h3></h3>
<h3>Sri Lanka</h3>
<p>It may seem like a small island but, Sri Lanka offers all the excitement of any larger tourist destination. It has protected areas for wildlife like leopards and elephants so your children can witness the wilderness. </p>
<h3></h3>
<h3>The United Kingdom</h3>
<p>You can learn about the UK’s history in museums and art galleries. The country is also home to Harry Potter and The Beatles. So, you can have a fun time with your kids while visiting tours and other experiences created around these pop culture giants. </p>
<h3></h3>
<h3>Thailand</h3>
<p>Thailand is very child-friendly, and it has so much to do. You can go snorkeling in the ocean or visit temples and chat with Buddhist monks. Thailand has something for everyone. </p>
<h3></h3>
<h3>Australia</h3>
<p>This massive island is one of the most diverse countries you or your kids will ever witness. It has ample wildlife, flora, and fauna. Most Australians speak English, so you don’t have to worry about a language barrier here.   </p>
<h2></h2>
<p>We hope that this list of Top 10 places to travel for families simplified your choices for you. Ensure you know the quarantine rules and regulations for any country before you finalize your visit. </p></div>
			</div>
			</div>
				
				
				
				
			</div>
				
				
			</div>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Five Financial Habits of Millionaires</title>
		<link>/2023/10/05/five-financial-habits-of-millionaires/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[eisel]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2023 20:37:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News & Insight]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://myfamilyaid.globalwebsitesadmin.com/?p=462</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<div class="et_pb_section et_pb_section_4 et_section_regular" >
				
				
				
				
				
				
				<div class="et_pb_row et_pb_row_4">
				<div class="et_pb_column et_pb_column_4_4 et_pb_column_4  et_pb_css_mix_blend_mode_passthrough et-last-child">
				
				
				
				
				<div class="et_pb_module et_pb_text et_pb_text_4  et_pb_text_align_left et_pb_bg_layout_light">
				
				
				
				
				<div class="et_pb_text_inner"><p>Millionaires may seem like an entirely different breed to some of us; however, they are humans like you and me. Self-made millionaires are those who come from nothing and grow to get everything. There’s great curiosity in the world right now about how such people are different from us common folk. Everyone is asking if there is a method to the madness of money?</p>
<p>We cannot answer the broader question of what habits and advantages lead to certain individuals becoming millionaires early in their careers. However, with the list of financial habits of millionaires we mention below, we hope to inform you of certain decisions you can take now so you can enjoy royalties in the future. </p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<h3>#1: They Stay Out of Debt</h3>
<p>This habit may seem like a no-brainer. Instead of signing up for a car or house that you can’t afford, buy one that you can. Cars and property that you buy in installments will cost you more than a car you would buy by saving up. Also, understand that using credit cards is also a way of accumulating debt. You should have a plan in which you pay for the expenses on your credit card every month. </p>
<h3></h3>
<h3>#2: They Live Below Their Means</h3>
<p>Millionaires don’t amass their wealth by acting like everyone else. They’re very unlikely to buy things because it’s a trend. Instead, their purchase decisions are driven by how much utility their purchase will bring. They look at how an item will bring substance to their living. Some millionaires may even go as far as saying they’re frugal. However, it’s about making the correct financial decisions. </p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<h3>#3: They Stick to a Budget</h3>
<p>Budgeting is one of the most important skills you can acquire in your adult life, and most millionaires have got it down to a science. An effortless way to budget your income is by using the 50-30-20 rule, meaning you can save up to 20% of your income every month. You have to make a plan for your money. Otherwise, you are likely going to lose it. </p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<h3>#4: They Invest Their Money</h3>
<p>Saving your income isn’t of significant use if you’re not using it to invest. Investing appropriately allows millionaires to take their income and increase it simply by having it. You should know how much money to invest and where to do so to get the maximum benefit from it. Check out all the schemes that banks and governments offer and choose your investment policy. </p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<h3>#5: They Ask for Advice</h3>
<p>Millionaires don’t know everything, and they don’t pretend to know everything. They have financial advisors who constantly give them the best advice regarding their money. You can find good financial advice from personal finance content creators on YouTube and other social media. Talk about your money and ask people for help! </p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<h3>Final Thoughts</h3>
<p>We couldn’t cover the many other financial habits of millionaires here. However, the most important idea is that of the mindset you have regarding your money. You have to create a mindset of wanting to save money and maximizing its potential in your life. Who knows? You might be the next big millionaire. </p></div>
			</div>
			</div>
				
				
				
				
			</div>
				
				
			</div>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>3 Ways for Managing Healthier Relationships With Yourself and Family</title>
		<link>/2023/10/05/3-ways-for-managing-healthier-relationships-with-yourself-and-family/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[eisel]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2023 20:34:09 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News & Insight]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://myfamilyaid.globalwebsitesadmin.com/?p=457</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<div class="et_pb_section et_pb_section_5 et_section_regular" >
				
				
				
				
				
				
				<div class="et_pb_row et_pb_row_5">
				<div class="et_pb_column et_pb_column_4_4 et_pb_column_5  et_pb_css_mix_blend_mode_passthrough et-last-child">
				
				
				
				
				<div class="et_pb_module et_pb_text et_pb_text_5  et_pb_text_align_left et_pb_bg_layout_light">
				
				
				
				
				<div class="et_pb_text_inner"><h3>3 useful ways to build and maintain healthier relationships and a stronger mindset:</h3>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<h3>1. Let Things go</h3>
<p>As humans, it is okay to make mistakes and not investigate them negatively; that way, you are on a healthy track to take a step back and rethink what could have gone wrong without beating yourself down.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<h3>2. Think for yourself</h3>
<p>Maybe you&#8217;ve confided things to family or friends, and they say something hurtful. It is okay to be confident in yourself and not let people control the way you feel about yourself.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<h3>3. Set Boundaries</h3>
<p>Have a game plan to do the things that can only benefit you and remember never to be pressured into anything that will not be beneficial to you in the long haul.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<h3>4. Know that it takes time and practice; here are some tools to help you navigate your self-care practice:</h3>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<h3>Habit Tracker</h3>
<p>Break bad habits by starting new healthy habits you want instead. You could pinpoint these as written goals and then start making sure of your progress with a Habit Tracker.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<h3>Goal Sheet</h3>
<p>Forgive yourself by treating mistakes as a new beginning to meet your short-term goals to give yourself happiness and fulfillment and get excited for rewarding good behavior every now and then with a treat for your progress.</p></div>
			</div>
			</div>
				
				
				
				
			</div>
				
				
			</div>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>A Family&#8217;s Guide to Frugal Spending</title>
		<link>/2023/10/05/a-familys-guide-to-frugal-spending/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[eisel]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2023 20:14:22 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News & Insight]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://myfamilyaid.globalwebsitesadmin.com/?p=452</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<div class="et_pb_section et_pb_section_6 et_section_regular" >
				
				
				
				
				
				
				<div class="et_pb_row et_pb_row_6">
				<div class="et_pb_column et_pb_column_4_4 et_pb_column_6  et_pb_css_mix_blend_mode_passthrough et-last-child">
				
				
				
				
				<div class="et_pb_module et_pb_text et_pb_text_6  et_pb_text_align_left et_pb_bg_layout_light">
				
				
				
				
				<div class="et_pb_text_inner"><p>Raising a child in the USA is not easy. The average cost of raising a child through 17 years is more than 200,000, and this does not include the college fee. Whether you are planning a child or growing brood, it pays to do a little budgeting and saving money from different means. Check out these money-saving tips that will change your family’s mindset about spending. </p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<h3>Guide to Frugal Spending</h3>
<p>Being born in a rich family is a privilege. However, most of the US population is middle class, while some of it is below the belt. Raising a child in economic crises is challenging, and you can never be too sure when the economy will fall. Here are some of our best spending tips for families. </p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<h3>Focus on the Cost of Food</h3>
<p>Learning how to save money while your family’s grocery bill is sky high is no easy feat. By adding a little discipline in eating and planning out your weekly meals, you can save a lot of money on grocery shopping. If your meal planning is weekly, tailor your shopping to bundle offers, and don’t buy things just to try them. This will improve your family’s health, and you will save money at the end of the month. </p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<h3>Plan Birthdays to a Minimum</h3>
<p>Going lavish on your child’s first birthday won’t help you or your newborn. Therefore, spending too much money on birthdays will end up eating your monthly budget. If you want to throw a big party, don’t order food from catering services. Plus, you can find some amazing DIY videos on YouTube for birthday decorations.  </p>
<h3></h3>
<h3>Try Secondhand Items</h3>
<p>Buying new clothes for your kids is a waste of money. Try buying secondhand clothes online or swap clothes with other families. This will teach your children about the value of money. It will bring you closer to other people. On the other hand, buying secondhand books or asking other families to lend them is also a good idea to save money. Try building better relationships with families with financial problems like yours. </p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<h3>Choose Fun AND Frugal Activities</h3>
<p>You might save a lot of money by planning small birthdays and buying secondhand items. Still, family activities are hard to tackle. Your kids might want to go for a vacation, and you can’t afford it. The best way to tackle this situation is to take your kids to the nearest community park every weekend. This will keep them happy, and they won’t ask for an expensive vacation in the Bahamas. </p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<h3>Ending Note</h3>
<p>Most families are struggling to put food on the table. Such families have a hard time surviving in an inflating economy. However, the tips we have shared above can help you save money for important things. So, keep your spendings on the low and saves on the high. </p></div>
			</div>
			</div>
				
				
				
				
			</div>
				
				
			</div>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Inside The Traditional Japanese Family Finest Cuisines</title>
		<link>/2023/10/05/inside-the-traditional-japanese-family-finest-cuisines/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[eisel]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2023 20:11:43 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Family Kitchen]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://myfamilyaid.globalwebsitesadmin.com/?p=447</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<div class="et_pb_section et_pb_section_7 et_section_regular" >
				
				
				
				
				
				
				<div class="et_pb_row et_pb_row_7">
				<div class="et_pb_column et_pb_column_4_4 et_pb_column_7  et_pb_css_mix_blend_mode_passthrough et-last-child">
				
				
				
				
				<div class="et_pb_module et_pb_text et_pb_text_7  et_pb_text_align_left et_pb_bg_layout_light">
				
				
				
				
				<div class="et_pb_text_inner"><p>Explore the origin story of your favorite traditional japanese treats including taiyaki, mochi, and okonomiyaki. </p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<h3>How Was Taiyaki Started?</h3>
<p>Taiykia originated in Japan in 1909 in a cake shop called Naniwaya Sōhonten. They are known for their imagawayaki, a delicious red bean cake dessert. At that time, the tai or red bean sea bream fish was a luxurious Japanese delicacy only the wealthy could afford. At first, he thought about the fish because he wanted to give everyone a taste of the elegant fish, and the idea came about. </p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<h3>How is Taiykia Made?</h3>
<p>To make traditional taiykia, all you need is a regular pancake batter in a taiykia fish mold with red bean filling. Nowadays, people use Nutella, cheese, breakfast sausages, eggs, and sandwich meats. </p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<h3>Where did This Mochi Deliciousness Come From?</h3>
<p>The delicious steamed rice paste dessert started in the ancient Japanese Jomon period, lasting between C. 14,000-300 BCE. It was known as mochitsuki, which is traditionally made during the New Year Festival. </p>
<p>You may wonder how did mochi and ice cream happen? Japanese American businesswoman Frances Hashimoto helped establish New York&#8217;s China Town in 1993. Hashimoto was president and CEO of Mikawaya, a confectionery producer specializing in Japanese pastries, and came up with the recipe when her husband gave her the idea. </p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<h3>Okonomiyaki is a Delicious WHAT Now?</h3>
<p>Okonomiyaki is a Japanese pizza pancake typically fried and made with: cabbage, egg, flour, tempura scalps, pork belly, dried seaweed, shrimp, calamari, scallops, pickled ginger, green onions, shiso leaves, and some variations include udon noodles. The traditionally used sauce is okonomiyaki sauce that can be store-bought or made from scratch for a more experienced chef. The sauce consists of 20 ingredients for a sweet yet savory flavor, including vinegar, vegetables, spices, and fruits. </p></div>
			</div>
			</div>
				
				
				
				
			</div>
				
				
			</div>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Cookie Decorating Ideas For The Whole Family</title>
		<link>/2023/10/05/workout-plans-for-new-moms/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[eisel]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2023 20:08:46 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Family Kitchen]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://myfamilyaid.globalwebsitesadmin.com/?p=442</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<div class="et_pb_section et_pb_section_8 et_section_regular" >
				
				
				
				
				
				
				<div class="et_pb_row et_pb_row_8">
				<div class="et_pb_column et_pb_column_4_4 et_pb_column_8  et_pb_css_mix_blend_mode_passthrough et-last-child">
				
				
				
				
				<div class="et_pb_module et_pb_text et_pb_text_8  et_pb_text_align_left et_pb_bg_layout_light">
				
				
				
				
				<div class="et_pb_text_inner"><p>A fun time with the family can start in the kitchen with a fun cookie decorating activity that can be enjoyed by the entire family. We recommend some DYI tips and cookie decorating essentials for your fun family baking project. </p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<h3>Cookie Cutters:</h3>
<p>You can get them with optional children-approved stencil cookie cutters rimes. Oddly enough, there are fun cookie cutters out there of all shapes, including your kids’ favorite characters. </p>
<h3></h3>
<h3>DIY Frosting Piping Bag:</h3>
<p>For precise frosting decoration, you can make frosting piping bags from 1-gallon Ziplock bags, a large cup, and scissors. Once you have your cup ready, place your flat hand upright in any corner of the Ziplock bag.</p>
<p>Then put your fingers together, creating a tip shape, and place your hand down in the cup. Then fold back a few inches of the bag and move the folds of the bag downwards gently. Then slowly place a spoon full of frosting into the bag. When the bag looks like it has the right amount, grab the end of the bag and bring it up to swirl the top of the pack. Once it is nice and tight, use the scissors to cut the tip. </p>
<h2></h2>
<h3>Cookie Dough Recipe</h3>
<p>Use your personal family recipe for cookies from scratch or you can get store-bought cookie dough that can help save some prep time. </p>
<h2></h2>
<h3>Easy Options:</h3>
<p>If you’re more about decorating and less interested in baking you can easily use store-bought products including icing, sprinkles, frosting, and baking mix. Another fun option is getting pre-made sugar cookies from the bakery department with a plain white frosting that can be customized with cute decorations. </p></div>
			</div>
			</div>
				
				
				
				
			</div>
				
				
			</div>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Why Are Older Men Attracted To Younger Woman</title>
		<link>/2023/10/05/why-are-older-men-attracted-to-younger-woman/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[eisel]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2023 20:05:56 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News & Insight]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://myfamilyaid.globalwebsitesadmin.com/?p=437</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<div class="et_pb_section et_pb_section_9 et_section_regular" >
				
				
				
				
				
				
				<div class="et_pb_row et_pb_row_9">
				<div class="et_pb_column et_pb_column_4_4 et_pb_column_9  et_pb_css_mix_blend_mode_passthrough et-last-child">
				
				
				
				
				<div class="et_pb_module et_pb_text et_pb_text_9  et_pb_text_align_left et_pb_bg_layout_light">
				
				
				
				
				<div class="et_pb_text_inner"><p>The savior complex usually comes from older men who want power over vulnerable, weaker people. Many of these men have experienced deeply hidden traumas they may not realize. Yet, they find themselves attracted to vulnerability in the form of a younger woman. </p>
<p>Some of these men grew up in a toxic family with parents experiencing mental illness who never gave them the total attention they needed. In this case, the older man will look for a younger woman without even realizing it. To feel like they can give that healthy relationship that they could not have with their parents.  </p>
<p>One reason is that the younger person will look at them in a different light because of all they do for them in these relationships. The dominant partner usually controls their spending habits or spoils them while being an older, wiser hero. That is one reason they don&#8217;t go for that older, more intelligent woman that&#8217;s their age.  </p></div>
			</div>
			</div>
				
				
				
				
			</div>
				
				
			</div>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
